&gt；&gt；Steve：所以我们谈了一点关于风格计算的问题。
&gt;&gt; Steve: So we talked a little
bit about style calculations.
这个链条的下一部分是布局和回流。
The next part of that chain
was layouts and reflows.
对，就像布局是有效的OK回流是有效的WE
Right, like a layout is effectively
ok a reflows is effectively a we
页面的布局。
layout of the page.
你用JavaScript改变了一些东西，不是吗？
You changed something with
JavaScript didn't you, right?
或者通过调整窗口的大小，因为我不知道当你做前端时
Or by resizing the window because I don't
know if whenever you make a front end
网页，非技术人员所做的第一件事就是查看它是否通过
webpage, the first thing a nontechnical
person does is see if it's responsive by
抓住一边，多次使窗户变小或变大。
grabbing the side and making the window
small and large a bunch of times.
技术人员也会这样做。
Also technical people do that.
我就是这么做的。
I do that.
我理解Chrome中所有响应性设计工具的位置，我不在乎。
I understand where all the responsive
design tools are in Chrome, I don't care.
[笑]所以，布局是第一次，一次回流
[LAUGH] So,
layout is the first time, a reflow
是一个经常使用的词，事情发生了变化，我需要更新布局。
is a word frequently used for, things have
changed, I need to update the layout.
布局可能非常昂贵，它们通常是主要原因之一
A layout can be really, really expensive
and they're usually one of the main causes
JavaScript，这会降低渲染速度，对吗？
of JavaScript,
that slow down rendering, right?
因为，是的，如果你做得太多，那就有问题了。
Because, yeah, if you do it too much,
that's problematic.
再次考虑页面上的所有元素，每个列表项，
Again think about all of the elements
on the page, every list item,
每个文本节点，所有内容，每个图像。
every text node, everything, every image.
这是很多工作。
It's a lot of work.
我甚至不知道它是如何在它完成的时间内完成的。
I don't even know how it gets it
done in the time that it does.
有点令人印象深刻，就像，
It's kind of impressive, like,
我认为这主要是因为我们已经有29年了，或者现在我认为网络是，
I think it's mostly that we've had like
29 years or now I think the web is,
29年来这样做的经验，使它相当快。
29 years of experience doing this,
has made it decently fast.
但就像难以置信一样。
But like it's incredible.
你可以实际上，有一些YouTube视频显示维基百科，或者
You can actually, there are some
YouTube videos that show Wikipedia, or
对于其他几个有效的页面，Firefox的过程是通过布局来完成的。
a few other pages effectively, the process
of Firefox goes through laying it out.
就像好的，有一个h1，它在div里面。
It's like okay,
there's an H1 it's inside of a div.
它不断地移动它，改变大小，调整东西，
And it keeps having to move it around and
change the size and adjust stuff and
这很吸引人。
it's fascinating.
所以之前提到过这一点。
So kind of mentioned this before.
只要元素的几何图形发生更改，浏览器就必须回流
Whenever the geometry of an element
changes the browser has to reflow
那一页对吧？
the page, right?
就像，实际上在浏览器中发生的情况是非常不同的，对吧。
Like, how that actually happens like in
the browsers is very different, right.
好像这真的无关紧要。
Like it doesn't really matter.
我们要讨论的主要问题是在你不需要的时候不去做，
The major points we're going to touch on
is not doing it when you don't need to,
这是最大的，对吧？
it's the largest one, right?
但是对于每个不同的引擎，实际的过程是非常不同的。
But the actual process is very
different for every different engine.
所以，你需要知道的关于回流的事情。
So, things that you need
to know about a reflow.
回流就是我们所说的阻塞操作。
A reflow is what we call
a blocking operation.
当我们向外转播页面时，其他一切都会停止。
Everything else stops when
we're relaying out the page.
你的JavaScript都没有运行，什么都没有，对吧？
None of your JavaScript is running,
nothing, right?
我们正在回流页面。
We are reflowing the page.
这就是我们现在正在做的事情。
That is the thing that
we are doing right now.
停止一切直到完成。
Stop everything until that is done.
显然，如果我没有把这一点说得足够清楚，那就很难了。
And obviously if I haven't made
this clear enough, it's hard.
而且它需要很多资源，而且不快也不容易。
And it takes a lot of resources and
it's not fast or easy.
如果你经常这么做，猜猜谁会注意到，对吧。
And if you do it a lot,
guess who's gonna notice, right.
我们尝试做的很多事情是，因为
A lot of the stuff we're trying to do is,
for
很多网络表现的东西，如果我们把工作做好了，
a lot of this web performance stuff,
if we're doing our jobs well,
用户应该永远不会注意到我们正在做任何事情。
the user should never notice
that we're doing anything.
用户从不去，他们隐含在他们的大脑里去喜欢，我喜欢这一面。
Users never go, they implicitly in
their brains go like, I like this side.
他们不知道表现是原因。
They don't know that
performance is the reason why.
但是，如果你这边的表现很糟糕，他们知道，[笑]对吗？
But, if performance on your side is
terrible, they know, [LAUGH] right?
如果用户注意到了性能，通常是您把它搞砸了，对吗？
If users notice the performance, it's
usually that you're messing it up, right?
所以你最终会在一个循环中做这件事。
So you end up doing this in a loop.
会很明显的，会很糟糕。
It's gonna be noticeable,
it's gonna be bad.
我们基本上不想让人们注意到我们。
And we basically don't
want people to notice us.
&gt；&gt；Steve：COO，l是唯一要保留的东西
&gt;&gt; Steve: Coo,l the only thing to keep in
思想是元素的回流。
mind is that reflow of an element.
我对这些话很小心，对吧。
I'm very careful with these words, right.
元素的回流导致其父级和子级的回流。
Reflow of an element causes the reflow
of its parents and children.
想想你对一棵树的了解。
Think about what you know about a tree.
[笑]如果你回流所有的孩子
[LAUGH] If you reflow
all of the children and
然后你回流父母，他们回流孩子。
then you reflow the parents and
they reflow the children.
纯粹的大多数时间，有一些边缘的情况下，你只能逃脱
Pure most the time, there are some edge
cases where you can get away with only
必须回流其中的一部分，我们将讨论其中一些。
having to reflow part of it and
we'll talk a little about some of those.
但一般说来，这是用来说
But generally speaking that is code for
saying
你碰了一样东西，你就碰了所有东西，对吧，这从技术上讲是事实。
you touch one thing you touch everything,
right, this is technically the truth.
但更多时候我会说95%的时间你回流一件东西，
But really more often I would say
95% of the time you reflow a thing,
你在回流一切。
you're reflowing everything.
祝你好运。
Good luck.
所以，好的，我们知道回流是昂贵的。
So, okay,
we know that reflows are expensive.
避免它们不一定是公平的，因为有时你确实需要改变
Avoiding them is not necessarily fair
cuz sometimes you do need to change
页面的那一层，对吧？
the layer of the page, right?
所以，它是你所需要的，也是尽可能少的可以逃脱的东西。
So, it's as much as you need and as little
as can get away with kind of thing.
那么是什么导致了回流呢？
So what causes a reflow?
这里有一个不完整的列表，是的，小字体是一个笑话，[笑]对吗？
Here is a incomplete list and yes,
the small font is a joke, [LAUGH] right?
这是一种将尽可能多的内容放在这张幻灯片上的方法，对吗？
It's a way to put as much on
this slide as possible, right?
调整窗口大小、更改字体、更改内容、添加或
Resizing the window, changing the font,
changing the content, adding or
删除样式表，添加或删除类，添加或删除元素。
removing a stylesheet, adding or removing
classes, adding or removing elements.
改变方向，就像你把手机从肖像带到横向，
Changing the orientation, like when you
take the phone from portrait to landscape,
显然，就像这样重排页面。
obviously, like that reflows the page.
计算大小或位置。
Calculating size or position.
那个很有趣。
That one's interesting.
试图找出大小或
The simple act of trying
to figure out the size or
某物的位置，导致回流。
position of something, causes a reflow.
令人着迷。
Fascinating.
改变大小或位置，就像是的，当然会导致回流。
Changing the size or position, like yeah,
of course that causes a reflow.
当你回流并改变一堆东西的大小时，
And when you reflow and
you change the size of a bunch of stuff,
猜猜你下一步要做什么？
guess what you got to do next?
对，你得重新粉刷，因为你现在需要
Right, you got to repaint,
because you now need
如果您更改了蓝色元素的大小，则将更多像素绘制为蓝色。
to paint more pixels blue if it's a blue
element that you changed the size of.
或多或少，我会给你一个提示。
More or less, I'll give you a hint.
布局是渲染管道中第二昂贵的部分。
Layout is the second most expensive
part of the rendering pipeline.
你想猜猜第一个是什么吗？
Would you like to take a guess
at what the first one is?
绘画，每次你回流，每次你做布局，你必须做的
Painting,and for every time you reflow
every time you do a layout you have to do
一种油漆，你猜怎么着，他们通常都是成套来的。
a paint, guess what, they always
come usually as a package deal.
那么问题是我们如何避免这种情况呢？
So questions how do we avoid this?
是的，你可以尝试，如果不能逃脱它的改变，就像最低级别的
Yeah,you can try like if can't get away
with it changing like the lowest levels of
DOM树而不是整个页面回流，
the DOM trees and
not get that whole page reflow,
比如让您将容器元素从600像素宽更改为800像素宽，
like give you change the container element
from 600 pixel wide to 800 pixels wide,
里面的一切都会改变。
everything inside of it is gonna change.
有时候你可以改变一个小得多的子集，但是
There are times when you can get away
with changing a much smaller subset but
将您的更改保持在尽可能低的树下。
keeping your changes as low
down the tree as possible.
停止修改内嵌样式就可以了，对吧？
Stop modying in-line styles will do it,
right?
你改变得越少，就越不能触发这些东西。
The less you change,
the less you can trigger this stuff.
我认为真正有趣的是交易的流畅性
I think a really interesting one
is the trade the smoothness for
速度，如果你正在做一个JavaScript动画。
speed if you're doing
an animation in JavaScript.
我们稍后再谈如何，
We'll talk later about how,
你可能不应该用JavaScript制作动画，但有时你需要这样做。
you probably shouldn't be doing animations
in JavaScript but sometimes you need to.
但需要考虑的是，我们之前谈过，
But the thing to think about is,
we talked a little bit before,
你的目标是每秒60帧。
the ideal you're aiming for
60 frames a second.
16毫秒对吗？
At 16 milliseconds right?
你看起来很酷。
You're like yeah cool.
所以在每一个小像素上，我希望这个动画是平滑的。
So on every little pixel I want
this animation to be smooth.
我想让每一个像素都有动画，对吗？
I want to animate every single pixel,
right?
如果这需要比你的16毫秒更长的时间
If that takes longer than
your 16 milliseconds and
你会错过那个画面的，对吧？
you're going to miss that frame, right?
因为你触发了所有的回流。
Because you're triggering all this reflow.
你最好一次移动那个盒子三个像素，对吧？
You're better off moving that box
three pixels at a time, right?
因为你实际上不会错过那么多帧。
Because you wouldn't have
actually missed as many frames.
所以有时候，把动画写得更简朴一些会让它更快
So sometimes, writing the animation to
be a little bit jankier makes it faster
因为你不会错过下一帧要画的画面。
because you don't miss the next
frame that's gonna be painted.
另一种是避免表格布局，这是有意义的
The other one is avoiding table layouts,
that kinds of makes sense for
有很多原因，有一个像我写类似的电子邮件，相信我。
a lot of reasons, one like I write
similar emails, just trust me.
[笑]好吧，这里的桌子很难，但另一部分就像，
[LAUGH] All right, a table here is hard,
but the other part is like,
如果列和表变得更宽，
if a column and a table gets wider,
你认为它上面和下面的其他细胞会发生什么？
what do you think happens like every
other cell above it, and below it?
它必须给予，你知道回流。
It's got to give, you know reflowed.
表的效果，定义它周围的一切。
A table effects,
everything around it by definition.
然后击倒操纵，这一个，如果你使用的是一个框架，
And then batting down manipulation,
this one, if you're using a framework,
你实际上是免费得到的，对吧。
you effectively getting it for
free, right.
这就是造成反应的原因，对吧？
This is what makes React, React, right?
它使Ember，和棱角分明，
It's what makes Ember, Ember, and Angular,
角度，就是他们知道如何获取你的应用程序的状态。
Angular, is that they figure out how
to take the state of your application.
并尽可能少地更改页面，
And do the bare minimum
of changing the page,
并且尽可能高效地做，对吗？
and doing it as efficiently as possible,
right?
所以，而不是，我将把所有这些加起来。
So, rather than, I'm gonna add all these.
就像，你会改变你的应用程序中的一大堆东西。
Like, you'll change a bunch
of stuff in your application.
它会找出一种形式上的方法来做到这一点。
It will figure out a pro
forma way to do that.
这就像是我们的很多框架
That is like legitimately
what a lot of our frameworks
会带到谈判桌上，对吧？
are bringing to the table, right?
是，我们将允许您对应用程序的状态进行一系列更改，
Is the, we will let you make a bunch of
changes to the state of your application,
我们将找到一种有效的渲染方式。
we will figure out an efficient
way of rendering it.
如果你没有使用框架，这是你的，对吗？
If you're not using a framework,
this is on you, right?
而且，就像不使用框架一样，总是很难做到的。
And like not using a framework
is always a toss up.
就像框架一样，我们也会付出代价，稍后我们会看到这一点。
Like Frameworks come with a cost,
that we'll see in a little bit.
对，他们不是免费的。
Right, they're not free.
你必须写得像它们是建立在JavaScript之上的，
You have to write like they
are built on JavaScript,
我们知道我们必须分离JavaScript并执行JavaScript。
we know that we have to part
JavaScript and execute the JavaScript.
他们做了很多必须是一般性的假设。
And that they make a lot of
assumptions that have to be general.
给定的框架必须对您有好处，因为它适用于
A given framework has to be as good for
you as it is for
坐在你旁边的人。
the person sitting next to you.
这意味着他们有点像所有行业的杰克，
Which means that they're are kind
of like Jack of all trades,
他们在做最好的假设。
they're making best case assumptions.
如果你要微调的话。
If you were going to fine tune stuff.
是的，就像你可能比你用Reaction做得更快，但是
Yeah, like you could probably make
it faster than if you used react but
你必须在所有事情上都这样做，很多时候我们做的交易
you'd have to do that for everything and
a lot of times we make the trade off of
一个框架在大多数情况下为我们做出正确的决定，对吗？
a framework making good decisions for
us most of the time right?
所以就像我们经常让他们对吗？
So that like we make
them more often right?
然后反驳课间休息事件，也就是说，如果你是这样的话，
And then debouncing recess events,
which is, if you are,
有一个没有事件的场景，它正在侦听要调整窗口大小的窗口。
have an eventless scenario that's
listening for the window to resize.
通常对我来说，如果我使用SVG进行数据可视化，就会发生这种情况
Typically for me, this happens if I'm
making a data visualization with an SVG
我想改变所有东西的宽度，就像窗口调整大小一样。
and I want to change the width of
everything, like when the window resizes.
他们通常拖着它。
They usually dragging it.
所以通常你不想重复这样做。
So usually you dont want
to do it repeatedly.
你说，好吧，我必须拖拽它，让我经常这样做，
You say, okay, I have to drag it and
let me do this every so often,
你会有更少的回流。
you'll have less reflows.